silabs.com 2014-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Silicon Labs

Silicon Labs appreciates your concerns about how personal information is used and shared. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting www.silabs.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

The information we receive from visitors to our website helps us to personalize and continually improve your experience. Itemized below are the various types of information we gather during your interaction with the website:

## Safe Harbor

Silicon Labs complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information obtained from European Union member countries and Switzerland and has self-certified its adherence to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement with the United States Department of Commerce. To learn more about the safe harbor program, and to view our certification, please visit www.export.gov/safeharbor. If you believe Silicon Labs is misusing your information or violating the Safe Harbor principles, please contact [DL.Privacy@silabs.com](mailto:DL.Privacy@silabs.com).

## Notice of Transfer, Use, and Storage of Customer Information  
(including Your Personal Information)

We will collect, use, and process certain customer information, including Personal Information (such as name, work email address, title, and employer name) for customer satisfaction and account management purposes. We may transfer certain customer information, which may include limited Personal Information, such as customer the contact information listed in this paragraph, to locations worldwide, such as each country in which Silicon Labs has an office, including the United States, which may not have the same level of data protection as your home country.

## Information You Give Us

We receive and store any information you enter on our website. We use the information you provide to respond to your requests, customize prospective features, improve the usability of our website, and to communicate with you.

## Automatic Information

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Like many websites, we use "cookies," to obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.silabs.com. There are portions of the www.silabs.com website that will not function without cookies enabled via your browser. As we explain in our Cookie Policy, you can choose to disable our cookies.

## E-mail Communications

To confirm your requests and provide you with requested updates, we will send you emails if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your communication preferences.

## Information from Other Sources

We will augment your user information with other relevant information received to further enhance your experience on the web.

We do not make information about users of our site available to outside parties.

## Affiliated Businesses

Some of our business affiliates, such as Digikey, Insight, and Mouser, operate stores on behalf of Silicon Labs. When a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party, you will be made aware of that fact.

## Protection of www.silabs.com and Others

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; protect the rights, property, or safety of www.silabs.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. This does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers on screen when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is your responsibility to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. An example of cited responsible behavior would be to sign off when have been using a shared computer.

## Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions 

When you visit www.silabs.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Texas. If you have any concerns about privacy at www.silabs.com, please send a thorough description to [admin@silabs.com](mailto:admin@silabs.com), and we will attempt to promptly resolve it.

As a consequence of business changes, our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use may be modified. We may periodically e-mail reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have specifically instructed us not to. We recommend that you check our website frequently to view recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all personal and account information we currently possess. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of information collected in the past without the consent of the affected users.
